#### Contact

prettyjoy2011@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pretty-joy-33533514b (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Web Development
Red Hat Linux
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

# **Pretty Joy**

I am a post graduate in Computer and Information Science with 2 year and 10 months total experience. I year industry experience as a junior Python Developer and 1 year 10 months as an Assistant Professor

India

## Summary

Software engineer with ability to learn and collaborate in rapidly changing environment and compositions. Eager to tackle web development/design challenges to achieve lasting impact on user experience

I am a postgraduate in Computer and Information Science with 2 years of teaching experience. And 1 year industry experience as junior python developer.

I have course completion certificate in Python with full stack development and red-hat system engineering course. Completed internship in python full stack development using django framework. Till now I published 3 conference papers in different journals. My skills include C, C++, HTML, CSS, PYTHON(DJANGO) SQL, Linux, Sqlite,

## Experience

Government Engineering College Idukki - India Assistant Professor October 2021 - May 2022 (8 months)

Kerala, India

#### WAHY LAB SOLUTIONS

Junior python developer September 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 1 month) Kochi, Kerala, India

### Education

College of Engineering ,Kidangoor

Master of Technology, Computer and Information Sciences, General  $\cdot$  (2017 - 2019)

College of engineering, Perumon

Bachelor of Technology - BTech · (August 2012 - April 2016)